前情提要  我叫霍普·迈克尔森
Legacies...  My name is Hope Mikaelson.
这些门后的学校
The school behind these gates
保护着像我一样藏着秘密的人
protects the secrets of people like me.
吸血鬼  狼人  女巫等等
Vampires, werewolves, witches  and everything in between.
怎么回事  兰登拿走了一把刀
What happened?  Landon took a knife.
那些本不该存在的怪物
Now monsters that shouldn't exist
从那之后就一直在追着那把刀
have been coming after it  ever since.
- 马里之洼是什么  - 那是一个地狱维度
- What's Malivore?  - It's a hell dimension
吞噬生物  并从集体意识中
that consumes creatures  and wipes their existence
抹去他们的存在
from the collective conscience.
老爸  我是不是坏掉了
Dad? Do you think I'm broken?
双胞胎之间发生了一些事
There's something that happens to twins
就如同你和乔西一样
like you and Josie.
当你们到22岁的时候
When you turn 22,
双子必须合并
the Gemini must merge.
所以  我们中的一个
So, one of us  is gonna have to kill
- 要杀掉另一个  - 我辜负了你们
- the other one?  - I failed you.
荣誉理事会将被召集并决定
The honor council will convene to decide
我是否留下来
whether I should remain
当你们的校长
as your headmaster.
我控制不了
I can't control it.
我们一直在怀疑他是不是有超自然能力
We've been wondering  if he's supernatural.
你没听说过凤凰的传说吗
You ever heard of the legend of the phoenix?
我没法控制我自己
I can't control myself.
用这个  唯一的缺点是
Use this. Only catch is,
你没法自己变回来
you can't turn yourself back.
我们的父亲是马里之洼
Our father is Malivore,
地表上有史以来最强大的怪物
the most powerful monster ever to walk the Earth.
我们的父亲
Our father?
如果我不阻止他  马里之洼就会崛起
And now Malivore's gonna  rise unless I stop him.
因为一旦我把自己扔进坑里
Because once I toss myself into that pit,
学校里就没人能记住我了
no one at school  will remember me,
包括你
including you.
六月
那里
Over there.
小兄弟
Hi, little brother.
暑假愉快
Have a great summer, guys.
9月再见
See you in September.
在塞瓦托尔学院
At the Salvatore School,
学年的结束对于不同的人来说
the end of the year means different things
有着不同的意义
to different people.
对于有些人来说是相聚
For some it's about reunions.
对其他人来说意味着离别
To others  it means saying goodbye.
夏天是开始新冒险的时间
Summer is a time to set out  on new adventures,
看看这个世界  以你从未想过的方式成长
see the world, to grow in ways you never imagined.
所有人都在前进
Everyone moves on.
米尔顿
Milton.
除了那些没地方去的人
Except for those  who have nowhere to go,
就像是我
the ones like me.
我叫做兰登·柯比
My name is Landon Kirby.
我只想知道我来自哪里
All I've ever wanted to know  is where I come from,
想要有个家  有个家庭  想要与众不同
to have a home, a family,  to be special.
最近 我都有了
Recently, I got all of it.
为什么我还觉得什么都没改变呢
So why do I feel  like nothing's changed?
总感觉我生命中
Somehow it feels like the most important piece
最重要的一块不见了
of my life is missing.
我知道我要继续寻找答案
I know I need to keep searching  for answers
因为据我所知
because as far as I can tell,
永生也意味着孤独
being immortal means  being alone.
而孤独就是
And being alone is...
绝望
hopeless.
吸血鬼后裔
第2季   第1集
妈妈没跟你说过这东西吗
Mom didn't tell you anything else about this thing?
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
唯一知道的是这东西叫做运星
Only that it's called an Ascendant,
是你我在5岁的时候和邦尼婶婶一起做的
and you and I made it with Aunt Bonnie when we were five.
这和双子有关吗
Does it have anything to do with the Merge?
我不知道
I don't know.
她对这口风很严  我
She's being cagey about it. I...
翻 译  噬魂师
抱歉  老妈差点让我断线了
Sorry. Mom almost busted me.
知道么  我们能像正常人那样面对面聊天
You know, we can Facechat like normal people.
我们不是正常人
We aren't normal.
我们需要在这个夏天提升我们的魔力
And we need to keep our magic sharp over the summer.
翻 译  马丁
- 治疗进行得怎么样  - 挺好
- How is therapy going? - Fine.
有个性感的瑞典人
There is this sexy Swedish guy
他的疗程就在星期二  我后面
whose session is after me on Tuesdays.
翻 译  兔兔秃了
我觉得他是瑞典人  也许是波兰人
I think he's Swedish. Maybe Polish.
这无所谓
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
他很性感
He is hot
翻 译  林中之王
很疯狂
and crazy,
语言的障碍会让我们
and the language barrier will make it impossible
无法交流
for us to communicate.
我就喜欢这样
Just how I like it.
- 你应该认真点  - 我会把它加进
- You should really work on that. I'll add it
需要粘合的碎片名单里
to the list of broken pieces to glue together.
你呢
What about you?
有火热的夏季约会吗
Any hot summer dates?
翻 译  霸气小肥鹅
自从老爸从校长的位置上离职后
Dad's been, like, my life plus-one
他就过得相当草率
ever since he got the headmaster boot.
我真觉得他正在经历中年危机
I honestly think he's going through a midlife crisis.
校 对   噬魂师
- 恶心  毛发变长了吗  - 毛茸茸的
- Gross. Hair growth?  - Bushy.
- 有女人缘吗  - 没有
- Lady prospects?  - Lacking.
特 效   麦 斯
你就没什么乐子吗
Are you not having any fun at all?
小不点儿威利•温克
What about
怎样
Wee Willie Winkle?
兰登大部分时间都独来独往
Landon's been keeping to himself mostly.
他总是和拉夫在一起
He's always off with Raf.
那就抛开一切  来欧洲吧
So ditch it all and come to Europe.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
不行  我不想丢下老爸一个人
I can't. I don't want to leave Dad alone.
说实话  我真担心他会去
I'm honestly kind of worried he's gonna go out
买一辆红色的小车
and buy a tiny red car.
我以为我们在独立这方面取得了进展
I thought we were taking strides to be less codependent.
确实
We are.
但还是有依赖的  而且不能放任
But there's codependent and then there's leaving Dad
老爸的胡子疯长
with his alarming mustache growth.
- 真恶心  - 是啊
- Oh, gross.  - Yeah.
有什么能帮你的吗
Can I help you?
是我  多利安
It's me, Dorian.
校长的人选 选得怎么样了
So how is the headmaster search going?
卡罗琳在缩小范围
Caroline's narrowing it down.
非常感谢你把这些东西借给我
I really appreciate you loaning me this stuff.
我明天去乔治亚州  我要在马里之洼
I'm headed to Georgia tomorrow. I'm gonna do another round
矿坑再做一次法医测试
of forensic testing on the Malivore pit.
如果有什么新消息  我会通知你的
If I learn anything new, I'll-I'll let you know.
我知道我对投票有点太激动了
I know I may have gotten heated over the vote.
确实
You did.
我也许反应过度了
Yeah, okay, I probably overreacted.
我只是没想到
You may have. Well, I just wasn't expecting
你会秘密投票
that you'd keep your vote a secret.
- 那是无记名投票  - 是的
- It was a secret ballot,  - Yeah.
当然  但是在你  乔西  卡莱布  杰德投票的时候
Of course. But between you, Josie, Kaleb and Jed voting,
我还在想怎么会出现三比一
I'm still wondering how three to one happened.
我以为你会投我一票
Yeah, I just assumed I could count on your vote.
祝好运  里克
Good luck, Ric.
真的很期望你能找到你找的东西
I really hope you find what you're looking for.
萨尔茨曼博士  好久不见
Dr. Saltzman. Long time no see.
我看到拉夫
I see Raf
比我吃的还要好
is eating better than I am.
要是你被永远困在狼形态
Yeah, well, you get stuck in permanent wolf form,
你也可以随便吃肉肉自助餐
and you, too, can hit the all-you-can-eat meat buffet.
有找到什么咒语把他变回来吗
Yeah. Any luck finding a spell to turn him back?
我在努力  还在想搞清楚
I'm working on it. Any luck figuring out
为什么我不记得我摧毁了马里之洼
why I can't remember destroying the Malivore pit?
我在努力
I'm working on it.
其他都顺利吧
Everything else good?
基本是
Totally.
弄完这些就行了
Here's to success.
唱歌给我听  宝贝  那是我想听的
Sing to me, baby. That's what I like to hear.
在乔治亚州炎热的夏日里
Sing to me like a vamp without his Daylight Ring
像个没有戴日光戒指的吸血鬼一样对我歌唱
on a hot Georgia summer day.
你应该记笔记
You're supposed to be taking notes.
重生
*  Back to life... *
你似乎没必要
Didn't seem necessary
全部都叙述出来
with you narrating the whole deal.
叙述是单向的  你听到的是一段对话
Narration goes one way. What you heard was a conversation.
- 和烤肉说话吗  - 烤肉也有名字的
- With your meat?  - Meat's got a name,
和你一样
okay, same as you.
这是格特鲁德
This is Gertrude.
我疯狂的叔叔厄尔  他在城外有个农场
My crazy Uncle Earl, he owns a farm outside the city.
她出生的那天  我就在那
I was there the day she was born.
这是可怕  老兄
That's dark, dude.
这是生命的循环  伙计
It's the circle of life, man.
完全天然的
All natural.
不自然的是你在那噘着嘴
What ain't natural is you over there pouting.
- 如果你这么说的话  - 不  我知道
- If you say so.  - No, I know so.
听着  你将要度过
Look, you're about to have
你人生中最美好的夏天  好吗
the best summer of your life. All right?
我很感激你为我做的一切  卡莱布
I appreciate everything that you're doing for me, Kaleb.
真的很感激  但这并不能改变
I really do. But it doesn't change the fact
我想念家人这一事实
that I miss my family,
即便他们很变态
even if they suck.
或者说我成了超级英雄
Or that I went full superhero
就在丽兹·萨尔兹曼觉得我很酷的时候
and then school ended just when Lizzie Saltzman
学期结束了
thought I was cool.
别说那名字  好吗
We don't say that name, okay?
甚至你的嘴巴都不要发出“丽”的音  一点都不要
Don't even fix your mouth to say Li-- none of that.
好吗
Okay?
就像我之前说的
It's like I was saying before,
我现在就是你的家人
I'm your family now.
也就是说  我的家人也是你的家人
Which means that my family is your family, too.
也就是说  你要开始
Which also means that you must start practicing
为7月4日在这屋顶上举行的烹饪比赛
for the cook-off that happens on this rooftop
进行练习了
every Fourth of July.
因为今年
Because this year,
我们要在我那疯子叔叔擅长的比赛里打败他
we're beating my crazy-ass uncle at his own game.
好吗
All right?
- 好的  - 好的
- Okay.  - Okay.
现在来些新鲜的动物血
Now you take some fresh animal blood.
欣赏这美丽的景色
Take in this gorgeous view.
我死而复生
*  I come back to life... *
深呼吸
Take a deep breath.
但没有用  没有
*  But that ain't gonna work, no... *
我们人生中最棒的夏天
Best summer of our lives.
没错  兄弟
Yeah, bro.
我死而复生
*  I come back to life... *
这肯定是格特鲁特的
Oh, that's straight Gertrude right there.
没错  没错  就是她
Yeah, yeah, that-that's her.
我不太擅长烹饪
I suck at this.
我最好的朋友曾经说
My best friend used to say
他宁愿饿死也不吃我做的东西
he'd rather starve than eat anything I tried to make, but...
你已经知道了
...you already know that.
很好
That's good.
我知道你在那  拉夫
I know you're in there, Raf.
我会找到办法让你变回来
I'm gonna find a way to get you back,
之后所有事都会重回正轨  好吗
and then everything will be good again, okay?
我不会放弃希望（霍普）的
I'll never give up hope.
喂
Hello?
【咒语】
Post tenebras spero lucem.
很高兴在这见到你
Fancy meeting you here.
你在这做什么
Whoa. What the hell are you doing here?
很明显  在救你的命
Saving your life, obviously.
不  我本应该归于平静的
No. I'm supposed to be in-in peace.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
你一点都不平静
Okay, you are not peace.
事实上  你是平静的反面
In fact, you're the opposite of peace.
我们在哪
So, where are we?
来  猜一下
Come on. Do the math.
没那么简单  这有奇怪的旋风
It's not that simple. Okay, there are freaky cyclones
漆黑一片  还有你在
and blinding lights and you're here...
天哪  我们在地狱
Oh, my God, we're in hell.
我想不是
No such thing. I think.
继续
Go on.
发挥你的想象力
Take your best guess.
不
No.
为什么不
Why not?
因为我不会让你洋洋自得的告诉我
Because I'm not gonna give you
我失败了
the satisfaction of telling me that I failed.
你是说你不想听到你在黑暗中
You mean you don't want to hear you're in the Blackness?
- 你被马里之洼吞掉了  - 不
- That you've been consumed by Malivore? - No.
你不想让我再说出你之前那些
You don't want me to point out that all your romantic heroics
浪漫的豪言壮语
were for nada?
那个大坏蛋还活着
That the big bad lives to see
而你所有的朋友
another day and all your friends
都忘却了你的存在
have forgotten you ever existed?
- 别说了  - 我要是你
- Stop talking.  - If I were you,
我会坦然接受
I'd make peace with that.
霍普
Hope.
等等
Wait.
我能帮你
I can help you.
我看不出来怎么帮
I don't see how.
我在这里度过了很多年
I spent years inside this place,
虽然你在马里之洼的肚子里开炮
and while you cannonballing into the belly of Malivore
似乎并没有毁了他
didn't seem to destroy him,
不过这改变了一些事
it has changed things,
所以别据我千里之外  也许我会详细说明下
so stop being a dick to me and maybe I'll elaborate.
好啊  那我洗耳恭听
Okay. I'm partially listening.
每一个被我父亲吃掉的生物
Every creature consumed by my father
都在这里被孤立开来
used to exist here in total isolation,
但我们就在这  互相交谈
but here we are, talking to each other.
你的出现不知怎么打开了
Your presence here has somehow opened
这里的牢门
the cell doors.
如果能做到这事
If it can do that,
也许有办法让我们逃出去
maybe there's a way for us to escape.
你怎么说
So what do you say?
合伙吗
Partners?
拒绝
Pass.
你就是个小屁孩  难怪你会失败
You are such a child. No wonder you failed.
一个一辈子都在辜负他老爸的人如是说道
Says the guy whose entire life has been about failing Daddy.
我不相信你  好吗  而且我永远不会相信你
I don't trust you, okay? And I never will.
是你让我陷入了如此困境
You're the one who brought me into this mess.
如果你让我把我那失败的弟弟做成肉傀儡
If you'd just let me meat-puppet my loser little brother,
那我们甚至都不会
then we wouldn't even be in...
【咒语】
Imitantor pupulis.
别再来了
Not again.
你的老朋友  模仿咒
Your old friend, the mimic spell.
我让你做什么  你就做什么
You will do anything I intend you to do,
我的意思是
and it is my intention
这将是我们最后一次谈话
that this is the last conversation we will ever have.
我要是你  我会坦然接受
If I were you, I'd make peace with that.
7月
我应该告诉你  上个月我搬家了
So I should probably tell you I moved rooms last month.
我们的房子正在粉刷  我想等你一变回来
Ours was getting painted, and I figured I'd move back in
我们就搬回去
once you were, you know, you again.
但要是我不在的时候你变回来了
But if for any reason you become you while I'm out,
例如出去找让你恢复的办法时
like, looking for ways to help you become you, I just didn't
我只是不想让你变回来后看到  我没有在我们的房间里
want you to go back and see that I wasn't in our room anymore
以为我抛弃你了
and think that I bailed on you,
因为我绝不会这样的  很显然
because I would never do that, obviously.
也没那么坏  对吧
And this ain't so bad, right?
我知道让你变回原样
I mean, I know it's taking a lot longer for us
比期望中花了更长的时间
to get you out of this mess than we both hoped, but...
你有了你自己的狼窝
...you got your own wolf den.
我们晚上看电影
We do movie nights.
7月4日快乐  兄弟
Happy Fourth of July, buddy.
无论我走哪条路  似乎都是死胡同
No matter what path I go down, it seems like a dead end.
我的意思是  马里之洼被毁的那晚
I mean, there were at least two other people with Landon
至少还有两个人和兰登在一起
the night Malivore was destroyed.
他们留下了纤维  脚印和头发
They left fibers, footprints, hair.
我只是不知道是哪两个
I just don't know who they were.
这不就是重点吗  如果有人
Isn't that the point? If somebody went into
进入了马里之洼  他们会从我们的记忆中被抹去
the Malivore pit, they'd be erased from our memories.
这就是困扰我的原因
Yeah, well, that's what's haunting me.
我们忘了谁
Who have we forgotten?
不可能是我们认识的人
It couldn't have been anybody we've known.
肯定会有留下的东西  照片
There'd be keepsakes, photos,
空床什么的
an empty bed somewhere.
无论他们是谁  他们对某些人都很重要
Well, whoever they were, they were important to somebody.
老爸  其实我很希望
So, Dad, I was actually hoping
我们能谈论下运星
we could talk about the Ascendant,
它和双子有什么关系
what it has to do with the Merge.
等等  在那的是兰登吗
Wait, is that Landon right there?
我已经埋头苦读了好几个星期的书了
I've had my head  buried in books for weeks,
却没有一本是关于如何把狼变回人的
nothing on how to turn a wolf back into a human.
我总是走进一个又一个的死胡同
I keep hitting dead end after dead end.
恭喜你加入死胡同俱乐部
Join the club.
兰登  你能问我父亲  为什么他不能告诉我
Landon, can you ask my dad why he won't give me answers
一个很简单的答案
to my very simple questions
我和我妹妹要如何活过22岁
on how my sister and I can survive past the age of 22?
那是因为你老爸
That's because your dad doesn't have
没有能给你的答案
any answers he's able to give you.
- 这就是原因  亲爱的  - 不能还是不愿意
- That's why, sweetheart.  - Able to or willing?
听着  关于运星  你什么都不需要知道
Look, there is nothing about the Ascendant you need to know.
那为什么我每次提到你都要避开
Then why do you flinch every time I bring it up?
因为它和双子没关系  乔塞特
Because it has nothing to do with the Merge, Josette,
不谈这话题了  好吗
so let's just drop it, okay?
我要回学校了
I'm gonna head back to campus.
烟火不看了吗
Whoa, what about the fireworks?
我担心它们会吓到拉夫
Oh, I'm worried they might scare Raf.
我不想它一个人
You know, I don't want him to be alone.
我和你一起
I'll come with you.
我瞬间没了庆祝的心情
I'm suddenly not in the mood to celebrate anything,
更不用说是单独庆祝
much less independence.
告诉我你想要从我这得到什么  孩子
*  Tell me what you want from me, boy... *
黛西  今天是个重要的日子
Okay, Daisy, today's the big day,
所以你的想法要软一点
so think tender thoughts.
拥抱这干燥的摩擦  与之融为一体
Embrace this dry rub, become one with it,
并且感谢
and thanks for, like,
你为我们献出生命什么的
dying for us and stuff, you know?
你在和烤肉说话
You talking to your meat?
你为什么不让我来治愈你
*  Why don't you just let me heal ya? *
那  那很奇怪  好吗
Nah, that'd, that'd, that'd be weird, right?
要是你不说才奇怪  一块很棒的牛排就像是植物一样
Be weird if you didn't. A great steak's like a plant.
你给它爱  它就会有回应
You love on it and it shows.
你伤害了我
*  You hurt me... *
我该说什么
What should I say?
你能把名字告诉我
Well, you can start by telling me your name.
米尔顿
Milton.
你老爸很恨你  还是怎么的
Your daddy hate you or something?
最近才这样  我的朋友们叫我MG
Not until recently, but my friends call me MG.
很高兴见到你  米尔顿
Then it's nice to meet you, Milton.
是时候翻下黛西了
It's time to flip Daisy.
你能从烟的颜色看出来
You can tell by the color of the smoke,
就像他们什么时候选教皇一样
like when they're electing a new pope.
你在摆布我
*  You're pushing me 'round... *
好吧
Okay. All right.
霍普
Hope.
我们能行的
We can work this out.
别这样对我
Don't do this to me.
听我说
Listen to me,
不管这是什么  这都会毁了你的
whatever this is, it's gonna destroy you.
这会让你万劫不复的
It'll rip you apart.
快把咒语解除让我来帮你
Please break the spell so I can help you.
霍普
Hope!
不用谢
You're welcome.
糟糕
Oh, crap.
这不是我想要的
Not exactly what I was expecting...
糟糕  快跑
Oh, crap. Run.
烟花的事情我改变主意了
I changed my mind about the fireworks.
没什么大不了的
It's not a big deal.
你觉得自己在跟谁讲话
Who do you think you're talking to?
我姐姐是自残女王
My sister is the queen of self-harm.
我一看到就知道了
I know it when I see it.
我不是在伤害我自己  因为没有东西可以伤害到我
I'm not harming myself because I can't be harmed.
这才是重点
That's the point.
无论在哪一个对凤凰的研究中
Where, in any of your phoenix research, does it say
都没说你能复活的次数是无限的
that the number of times that you can resurrect is infinite?
也没说不是
Where does it say it isn't?
伤害自己也于事无补
Hurting yourself doesn't make anything better.
向来如此
It never does.
你说得对  也许我可以把注意力放在别人身上
You're right. Maybe I should focus on other people's problems
而不是我自己
instead of my own.
- 我没有这么做  - 你在说谎
- That's not what I'm doing. - That's a lie.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
因为如果你也像我以前那样谎话连篇的话
Because when you lie as often as I used to,
你就会第六感了
you develop a gut feeling.
- 我就是知道  - 好吧
- I just know. - Okay.
我们该怎么做
What are we supposed to do?
你说呢
You tell me.
因为说实话  我现在有点懵
Because, to be honest with you, I'm kind of at a loss.
也许我们俩都不必再那么害怕死亡了
Maybe we should both stop worrying so much about dying.
试着活在当下吧
Start living a little?
乔
老时光  烧烤调味酱
你好 卡莱布
Hey, Kaleb.
放松点  老卡
Relax, Special K.
只是烧烤而已
It's just barbecue.
听我说  我现在在你旁边
Now, look here, I stood by you
就会想到你杀了我们的一个朋友
when I thought you murdered one of our friends.
- 好吧  - 但是你只要再说一句这样的蠢话
- Okay.  - But you say something stupid like that again,
我们就别做朋友了  兄弟
we ain't brothers, man.
好吧
Okay.
该死
Damn.
又有人投了我的变态舅舅一票
Another vote for my creepy-ass uncle.
我是厄尔
I'm Earl.
- 米尔顿  米尔顿·格雷斯利  - 没错
- Milton, Milton Greasley. - That's right.
我听说过你
I heard about you.
希望是关于我的好事
Good things, I hope.
可不是吗  吸血鬼  都是好事
Yeah, bloodsucker, all good.
你骗到他了
You got his ass.
嗨  我尝了你做的肉了
Hey, I tried your meat.
- 味道怎么样  - 第二妥妥的了
- Yeah? - Solid second place.
颁奖台上见了
See you on the podium.
是啊  但是这次你要抬头看我了
Yeah, but this time you'll be looking up.
你真的觉得我们会赢吗
Do you really think we can win?
当然  我知道我们可以的
Hell no, man. I know we can.
就像我一直说的那样  这是最棒的一个夏天
It's like I've been saying: best summer ever.
- 是啊  是啊  - 你看看啊
- Yes, sir. Yes, sir. - Look at this.
关于这个嘛  我可能遇到我的真爱了
Um, about that, I may have found someone.
- 就是这件事  - 是吗
- That's what's up.  - Yeah.
- 她来了啊  - 来了
- She here? - Yeah.
- 是哪一个  - 穿橘色上衣的那个
- Oh, which one? - Uh, orange top.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
最棒的夏天了
Best summer...
不会吧
Never.
你是说凯姆吗
You're talking about Kym?
她叫凯姆吗
Is-is that her, is that her name?
MG  你在开玩笑吗
MG, are you kidding me?
我给你说过多少关于凯姆的故事了
I've told you a million stories about Kym.
凯姆  我
Kym. I...
你妹妹吗
Your sister?
就是那个离家给流浪汉造房子的那位吗
Th-The who was away, building houses for homeless people?
没有这些
And without all of that...
听着  兄弟
Look, man,
这夏天你怎么找乐子都行
have all the summer fun you want.
但是千万别跟她扯上关系
Just don't be having it with her.
爱是答案
* Love is the answer *
Better Together - Jack Johnson
至少是我心里想的大部分问题的
* At least for most of the questions in my heart *
我们为什么在这里
* Like "Why are we here?" *
我们又去哪里
* And "Where do we go?" *
为何如此艰难
* And "How come it's so hard?" *
它不总是那么轻而易举
* It's not always easy and sometimes *
生活可能会骗你
* Life can be deceiving *
我告诉你一件事情
* I'll tell you one thing *
我们在一起  心情更美丽
* It's always better when we're together *
是的  我们在一起  心情更美丽
* Mmm, it's always better when we're together *
是的  我们在一起数星星
* Yeah, we'll look at the stars when we're together *
是的  我们在一起  心情更美丽
* Well, it's always better when we're together *
* Yeah, it's always better when we're together... *
什么
What?
写歌  别了吧
Songwriting? Stop.
我受不了了
I can't take it anymore.
在比利时的某个地方
Somewhere in Belgium,
8月
佩内洛普公园的黑心爆炸了
Penelope Park's black heart just exploded.
你和小发明是小妖精吗
You and Gizmo the Gremlin?
实际上  小发明是魔鬼
Actually, Gizmo's a Mogwai.
哦  天啊
Oh, God.
你跟他在一起都开始疯言疯语了
He's got you speaking nerd.
- 放松  我们只是朋友  - 你们才不是朋友
- Relax. We're just friends. - You are not friends.
- 你是一个蒙太奇  - 和他一起
- You're a montage. - It's been...
很有意思
fun.
真的很有趣
It's been, like, actual fun.
你知道什么才是真有趣吗
You know what's actual-actual fun?
妈妈和我在商量
Mom and I taking
周末的时候坐高速列车到罗马
the speed train to Rome for the weekend.
所以快点横跨大西洋过来吧
So get your ass across the pond.
爱你哦
Love you.
你觉得我们在这里多长时间了
How long do you think we've been here?
很难说啊
Hard to say.
一周  一个月
A week? A month?
一年  有什么区别呢
A year? What difference does it make?
那是什么鬼
What the hell was that?
石像鬼吧  我猜
Uh, a gargoyle, I think.
我和朋友以前杀过一只
I killed one once with my friends.
我青少年时候的朋友
You know, my teenage friends.
那为什么像你这样的超级大坏蛋会害怕呢
So why is a supervillain like you scared?
我不是坏蛋
I'm not a villain.
从来都不是
I never have been.
我只是一个从小害怕自己的父亲
I'm just a kid who's afraid of his father
并且为了离开他愿意做任何事的小孩
and will do anything to get away from him.
我这一辈子都在想怎么离开他
My entire life's been about figuring out how.
然后悲惨得失败了
And failing miserably.
【咒语】
Papilio lux.
你觉得这是我们出去的钥匙吗
You think that's our ticket out?
不是  这只是一个安慰的咒语
No. It's a comfort spell.
为了让心得到平静
It's, it's supposed to provide peace of mind.
谢谢你
Thank you.
- 为什么要这么做  - 做什么
- Why did you do that? - Do what?
糟糕
Oh, crap.
- 隐形  - 什么意思
- Invisique. - Meaning?
他们看不到我
I'm invisible to them.
你是隐形了  那我呢
You're invisible. What about me?
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
因为我们毕竟是拍档
Guess we're partners after all.
- 我可没这么说  - 但是你刚才确实救了我的命
- I didn't say that. - But you did just save my life.
因为你有些事没跟我说  我想知道为什么
Because you're keeping things from me, and I want to know why.
【咒语】
Veritas tempus.
你能不能不要念咒语了  这不公平
Would you stop with the magic already? It's not fair.
在回答之前先好好想想
Think before you answer.
是不公平还是咎由自取
Is it unfair, or do you deserve it?
完全是我咎由自取
I totally deserve it.
什么
What?
为什么我刚才会这么说
Wh-Why-why did I just say that?
因为我刚才念的是真相咒语  你只能跟我说实话
Because I cast a truth spell. You can only answer me honestly.
现在你感觉如何
Now, how does that make you feel?
感觉我不会有什么好下场
Like this isn't gonna end well for me.
我每天五点给他送晚饭  我是说  有时候
I bring him dinner every day at 5:00. I mean, sometimes
他不是从树林里来的  但是他永远都会在这里
he doesn't come out of the woods, but he's always here.
这也不能说明发生了什么是  拉夫是匹狼
Well, that doesn't mean something happened. Raf's a wolf.
- 他又不戴手表的  - 但是每天
- It's not like he wears a watch. - But every day,
乔西  几个月以来  已经三天了
Josie, for months, and it's been three days, and...
也许我想的是最坏的情况
Maybe I am just assuming the worst,
但是往往最坏的情况就会发生  如果他作为一匹狼
but the worst is usually what happens. And it's bad enough
被困在什么地方就已经很糟糕了  但是如果他迷路了
that he's stuck as a wolf, but if-if he's lost,
他身边一个人都没有
he's got no one.
- 我不能让他一个人啊  - 兰登
- I can't let him be alone.  - Landon.
会没事的
It's gonna be okay.
我们找到他的  我来做一个定位咒语
We're gonna find him. I'll do a locator spell,
我们会追踪到他的行踪  好吗
and we're gonna track his movements, okay?
我会帮你的
I'm gonna help you.
一直以来
This entire time,
我一直在研究一个理论
I've been working on a theory, you know,
试图找出漩涡出现的原因
trying to figure out why the vortex comes.
后来我发现  它总是在我施了魔法之后出现
And then I realized, it's always after I do magic.
我说得够清楚了吗
Am I getting warm?
非常清楚
Scalding.
当你开始思考这个的时候  就会显得很有意义
You know, it makes a lot of sense when you think about it.
我以为我是唯一可以毁灭他的人  我想错了
I thought that I was wrong about me being the only one
但我觉得我真正的错误是
who could destroy him, but I think my actual mistake
当我坠入黑坑时
was that I, I wasn't a fully activated Tribrid
我不是一个完全被激活的三方混血
when I dove into that pit.
我从未死过  所以我吸血鬼的一面还没有被激活
I've never died, so my vampire side hasn't been activated yet.
现在我意识到马里之洼
And what I'm realizing now is that Malivore
不欢迎我在这里
doesn't want me here.
我对他来说是有毒的
I'm toxic to him.
把那句话说完好吗
Finish that sentence, please?
马里之洼想驱逐你
Malivore's trying to expel you.
要把你送回你来时的地方
To send you back from where you came.
- 每次他尝试  - 我抓住了你
- And every time he tries... - I grab hold of you
想和你一起被驱逐
to try to get expelled with you.
虽然我父亲很想让你离开
But as much as my father wants you to leave,
他还想在这里继续折磨我
he wants to keep torturing me here even more.
官方一点说
Then it's official.
我们要做的就是等待
All we have to do is wait.
为了什么
For what?
这是我的旅程
That's my ride.
霍普  你不能把我留在这里
Hope, you can't leave me here.
我不能带你走  好吧
I can't leave with you. Okay?
我得回去找我的朋友们
I have to get back to my friends.
我要回去找兰登
I have to get back to Landon.
我不能撒谎  对吧
I can't lie, right?
所以你知道我说的是实话
So you know I'm telling the truth when I say that if you
如果你不带我回去
help me go back, too,
你永远不会再见到我了
you'll never see me again.
我保证
I promise.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
但是你知道我为什么不能冒这个险吗
But do you understand why I can't take that risk?
我知道  如果我是你  我也会这么做的
Yeah. I would do the same thing if I were you.
- 天啊  - 祝你好运  克拉克
- God. - Good luck, Clarke.
去你的  霍普
Screw you, Hope.
我的血就像夺宝奇兵
Think of my blood like the red line crossing the map
地图上的红线
in Raiders of the Lost Ark.
它会流向能感应到拉夫的任何地方
It'll flow wherever it senses Raf.
它会告诉我们路径
And it'll show us the path.
谢谢你
Thank you for this.
老实说  这是小孩的把戏
Of course. It's honestly child's play.
我以前玩捉迷藏的时候就是这样作弊的
It's how I used to cheat at hide-and-go-seek.
就
And just
稍微等一会
give it a second.
我想让你知道  我并不想伤害自己
I want you to know, I wasn't trying to hurt myself.
7月4号的时候
On the Fourth.
我不是想
I wasn't trying to, like,
自毁什么的
self-destruct or anything.
你差点就骗过我了
Mm, could've fooled me.
我不知道  也许一开始是这样
I don't know. Maybe it started like that,
但是当我下潜的时候   我看到了一些影像
but when I go under, I see... images.
也许是记忆
Memories, maybe.
我死的时候  我的脑子里藏着一些东西
There's something buried in my brain, and when I die,
我瞥见了  但是
I get a glimpse of it, but...
也许什么都没有
Maybe it's nothing.
也许这就是所有问题的答案  我不知道
Maybe it's the answer to everything. I don't know.
没有什么比确保
No answer is more important than making sure
你不会不小心超过你能起死回生的次数更重要的了
that you don't accidentally overshoot your phoenix quota.
你快乐吗
Are you happy?
- 你是什么意思  - 我是说
- What do you mean? - I mean,
自从我们开始约会
since we started hanging out--
我是说  直到拉夫失踪之前  我想我
I mean, until Raf went missing-- I think I was
终于开始
finally starting to get...
收获快乐了
happy-ish.
我肯定很开心
I'm definitely happy-ish.
我就是不知道  在我知道莉齐和我必须经过合并才能活下来之后
I just don't know if I can be fully happy until I know
我是不是还能真的快乐起来
that Lizzie and I are gonna survive past the Merge.
是的
Yeah.
听着  我不想多管闲事
Look, I don't want to cause problems,
但我觉得关于运星的事
but I think that your dad is lying to you
你爸爸在对你撒谎
about the Ascendant.
你怎么知道的
How do you know?
我就是知道
I just know.
带我去野外
* Take me to wild *
带我去水边
* Take me to the water... *
你是法医侦探吗
Forensic detective?
接近了
Close.
真正的犯罪小说家
True crime novelist.
你是一个骗子
You're a liar.
乔西  你不能来这里
Josie. You can't be in here.
- 她不能来这里  - 是  我知道
- She can't be in here. - Yeah, I'm aware.
给我点时间
Just give me a second.
- 怎么了  - 整个夏天
- What's going on? - All summer
我一直在担心你
I've been worried about you.
一定要照顾好爸爸  确保他不会
"Got to take care of Dad, make sure that he doesn't fall
抑郁又或者买辆摩托车
into a depression or buy a motorcycle."
我放弃和妈妈一起过暑假是为了确保
I gave up my summer with Mom to make sure
你不会孤单一人  这整段时间以来
that you wouldn't be alone, and this entire time
关于运星的事  你一直在对我说谎
you've been lying to me about the Ascendant?
我  我要报警
I... I'm calling the cops.
让他和他女儿好好谈谈
Let the man talk to his daughter.
带我走向光明
* Take me to the light... *
爸爸  你怎么能这样
Dad, how could you?
爸爸把一切都告诉我了
Dad told me everything.
运星是通往
The Ascendant is a lock
监狱世界的锁
to a prison world.
说来话长  但我们有一个叔叔被困在那里
It's a long story, but we have an uncle
他是我们这个疯子家族中
that is trapped down there, and he is the only other
唯一活着的其他成员
living member of our lunatic family.
他已经通过了合并  所以他一定知道答案
And he's been through the Merge, so he's got to have answers.
那等我一回来我们就走吧
Well, then let's go the minute I get back.
丽兹
Lizzie,
我把运星还给了爸爸
I gave the Ascendant back to Dad.
什么  为什么
You what? Why?
被困在那里的那个家伙和爸爸
This guy that's trapped down there killed Jo
在乔结婚那天
on her wedding day
杀了乔
with Dad.
我是说  这家伙杀了他的双胞胎兄弟
I mean, this guy murdered his twin.
爸爸说这是最后的办法了
So, Dad said it's a last resort.
在那之前  我们应该远离它
And until then we should just stay far away from it.
与此同时
So, in the meantime
你应该好好享受
you should enjoy
你的高速列车
your speed trains and hang out
和瑞典帅哥一起出去玩  享受你的夏日乐趣
with hot Swedish guys and have your summer fun.
听着
Listen.
我每天治疗三小时
I'm in therapy three hours a day.
我不是和心理医生在一起  我就是和医生在一起
When I'm not with a shrink, I'm with a doctor.
不是跟医生在一起  就是跟治疗师在一起
And when I'm not with a doctor, I'm with a healer.
我尽我所能让自己变得更好
I'm doing everything I can to get better,
真的很好的样子
like, really better.
我应该告诉你的  我不知道为什么我没有说
I should have told you that. I don't know why I didn't.
但是答应我
But promise me
你会好好利用
you will make the most
这个夏天剩下的时间  好吗
of the rest of this summer, okay?
我保证
I promise.
我没看见你  你还好吗
I didn't see you. Are you okay?
是的  多利安  我没事
Yeah, Dorian, I'm okay.
很高兴听你这么说  但是你怎么知道我的名字的
Glad to hear it, but how did you know my name?
你的停车证写着呢
Your parking pass.
多里安·威廉姆斯
泊车许可证
我一直讨厌那张照片
Always hated that picture.
什么风把你吹来了
What brings you out here tonight?
一个男孩
A boy.
里面都锁上了
Well, we're all locked up in there.
大家都去度暑假了
Everyone's gone for the summer.
好吧  谢谢  抱歉打扰你了
Okay. Thanks. Uh, sorry to bother you.
你自己开始了
You started without me.
你的地图成功了
Your map worked.
- 他就在这里  有什么问题吗  - 他曾经在
- He's right here. What's the problem? - He was,
但当我出来找他的时候  就出现了
but then when I came out here to find him, that appeared.
拉夫没有失踪
Raf's not missing.
他只是不想
He just doesn't want
不想待在这里了
to be here anymore.
我就知道会这样
I knew this going in.
我是说  他是狼人的时间越长  像人的地方越少
I mean, uh, the longer he's a wolf, the less human he'll be,
在什么情况下  狼人不再需要一个最好的人类的朋友
and at what point does a wolf no longer need a human best friend
和电影之夜
and movie nights?
但我有很多话要说
* But I've got a lot to say... *
也许他已经离开了
Maybe he moved on.
因为他看到你有一个
'Cause he saw that you have someone
可以帮助你
who can help you be
获得快乐的人
happy... ish.
感觉过了好久
* Well, it feels many moons away *
但我终究还是为你而来
* But I came for you *
我曾梦到你的名字
* I've dreamt names for you *
是那么真实
* It's true *
没有人能像你一样让我如此兴奋
* No one makes me high like you do. *
你好
Hey.
旁边的位子空着吗
Is this seat taken?
兰登
Landon.
撒谎
* Lying... *
等一下  你是怎么知道我名字的呢
Wait, how do you know my name?
抱歉
Sorry.
我绝不会假装忘记霍普·迈克尔森
There's no way I'd even pretend to forget Hope Mikaelson.
你会这么说  是因为你知道我想听
You're just saying that because you know I want to hear it.
其实  不是这样的
Well, actually, that's not how this works.
我来这里  是为了跟你说一些
I'm kind of here to tell you the things
你不想听的事情  你知道的吧
you don't want to hear, right?
嗯
Yeah.
在每条路的尽头
* At the end of every road *
你都在守候着我
* You were good to me... *
我是真的想要见你
I really needed to see you.
这让我很开心
Happy to be seen.
我的意思是  正如魔法中显现的那么开心
Well, I mean, as happy as the magical,
我的潜意识  我的所思所想  已经暴露无遗
holographic manifestation of your subconscious can be.
那么  你在想什么呢
So what's on your mind?
我想念你的眼眸
I missed your eyes.
承认吧  它们深邃迷人  如同星夜
Oh, admittedly, they're pretty dreamy.
言过其实
So much for accuracy.
- 兰登从不会这么说话  - 创造是自由的
- Landon would never say that. - Well, it's creative license.
另外  我们直面这个问题  你已经
Besides, let's face it, you already know
知道  他会谈到  你如今的窘境
what he'd say about your current dilemma.
- 可能  我把你造出来  就是想听你谈那件事  - 好吧
- Then maybe I just want to hear it from fake you.  - Fine.
在那种情况下
Then, in that case, there is no world
在任何一个世界  我都不会希望
in which I would ever want you to leave town
你没告诉我你死而复生了  就这么离开了
without telling me you're back from the dead.
严格地说  我没有死
I never died, technically.
我也想听听你怎么说
Then I'd want to hear about that, too.
我想知道一切
I'd want to hear about everything
因为我爱你
because I love you,
你也爱我
and you love me.
你离开城镇的做法
You leaving town
是愚蠢至极的  你心里清楚
is a stupid move and you know it.
尤其是当我们互相说好  不再欺骗对方以后
Especially after we agreed not to lie to each other.
别把矛头指向我
Don't turn this around on me.
好吧  除此之外   你和乔茜之间怎么了
Okay, besides, what's happening between you and Josie?
我已经习惯了放手
* And I'm so used to letting go... *
- 你还生我的气吗  - 没有
- So you're mad at me?  - No.
我没有生你的气
I'm not mad at you.
我不能对你生气  不是吗
I can't be mad at you, right?
你又没错
It's not your fault.
你都不知道我的存在
You don't even know I exist.
但这还是很伤人
But that still hurts.
确实如此
Of course it does.
好吧
Okay.
那么  你再想想  当我发现你一声不吭就离开的时候
So, then think about how much it would hurt me to find out
我会有多难过
you're just down the road.
非常非常
Fair enough.
曾经轻狂  践踏真心
* Hearts I've broke *
而今悔恨  泪流不止
* Now my tears flow *
如果你能正确地回答这个问题
If you can answer this one question correctly,
那我发誓  我会回到你的身边
then I promise I'll go running back to you,
告诉你所有的真相
and I'll, I'll tell you the whole truth.
你能别再玩游戏了吗
Would you quit playing games?
我们现在都没有办法
There is no answer either of us could give
阻止你做这事
that should stop you from doing that right now.
你快乐吗
Are you happy?
现在我轻轻关上心门
* And now I'm closing every door *
现在  每个人更快乐了吗
Is everyone happier now?
我不再想着  索取更多
* 'Cause I'm sick of wanting more *
于我而言  你已足够珍贵
* You were good to me *
如此珍贵
* You were good to me... *
你能让我一个人安静会吗
Could you leave me for a minute?
我不想让你看到  我在流泪
I don't really want to cry in front of you,
即使你不是真的
even if you're fake.
我不会再伤害到你了
* I won't hurt you anymore *
你于我  如此珍贵
* 'Cause you were good to me. *
所以说  似乎是我让你扫兴了  是吗
So you, uh, feel like I let you down, huh?
没有
Nah. Nah.
无疑是史上最棒的夏天
Uh, best summer ever's a big ask.
伙计  你总是这么的吗
Man, why do you always do that?
- 什么  - 把话都憋在心里
- What?  - Not speak your truth.
好吧  这个夏天过得很糟糕
Okay, this summer sucked.
我是说  你让我向前
I mean, you tell me to move on,
第一次  我确实照做了
and the first time I actually do,
你让我别和她说话
you tell me I can't even talk to her.
她是我的妹妹啊  伙计
She's my sister, man.
就像  你是我的兄弟
Just like you're my brother.
抱歉  我想让我家族繁荣  开枝散叶
I'm sorry, but I want my family tree to have branches.
但如果  有机会  我会补偿你的
But I'll make it up to you if you give me a shot.
怎么补偿
How?
给你世界上  你最想要的东西
By getting you what you want most in the entire world.
丽兹·萨尔茨曼
Lizzie Saltzman.
你  你说过  我们不该说起她的名字了
You-you said we-we weren't supposed to speak her name.
那是在夏天
during the summer,
但现在  一切都结束了  男孩
but that's all over with, baby boy.
现在  让我们把目光投向
Now we set our sights on
有史以来最好的学期
best semester ever.
好吗
Okay?
先把行李打包好
Let's finish packing.
你得腾个地方  放这个
And you should definitely make room for this.
该死
Oh, crap.
难以相信这又发生了
I can't believe this is happening again.
父亲  你从我这里想得到些什么
What do you want from me, Father?
我真的不能再忍受一分一秒了
Because I literally cannot suffer anymore.
毫无疑问
And... make no mistake,
你创造了我
you did make me, so...
请  最后再给我次机会  让我服务于您
please give me one final chance to serve you.
把我送回去
Send me back.
神秘瀑布镇
送我回去
Send me back
我会变成  你想让我成为的样子
and I will be what you always wanted.
我会变坏
I'll be the bad guy.
你会以我为荣
I'll make you proud.
你需要我
You need me.
如果你是不相信  我能让你起死回生
Because if you do not trust me to raise you from perdition,
相信我  我会做到的
trust that I will do this.
我会手刃霍普·迈克尔森
I will destroy Hope Mikaelson,
那是  在这个星球上  唯一能杀掉你的
the only thing on this planet that can destroy you.
你送我回去  我会
You send me back, and I...
父亲
Father?
是你吗
Is that you?
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）